# Cristofer Hernandez

Developer

+44 7519307667 cristofer.pro@icloud.com https://cristoferjimenez.uk/ lpswich, England

#### SUMMARY

Dedicated and friendly programmer with a background in IT. Currently, offering freelance roles for companies, I was graded distinction undertaking my education in college, I learnt Software development, Web Development and Mobile Apps Development with languages such as Java, Python and Bootstrap 4 framework. In my personal time, I have taken self-education learning C# and other various programming languages. I am Inclined to utilise my skills in coding to create practical software with a heavy emphasis on great user experience.

#### EXPERIENCE

06/2020 - Present

# **Trading Financial Markets**

Self employed

- · Understanding how fundamental and technical data converge.
- · Consistently met my short and long-term targets.
- · Reading fundamental data.
- · Understood technical analysis.
- · Following a consistent strategy
- · Following Projections.
- · Risk management.

06/2021 - 06/2021

## **Project manager (Work Experience)**

Norfolk Community Advice Network (NCAN)

- Gathering client requirements and processing them into a gantt chart.
- · Taking responsibility of the project and attending meetings.
- · Delivered a fully working website within a one week period.
- Creating teams within the project to handle different tasks.
- Dealing with pending requirements and technical issues.
- Documenting the project PID upon every changes.
- · Team collaboration.

03/2020 - 03/2020

## **Assistant (Work Experience)**

Barclays

- Site safety & security.
- · Risk assessment & confidentiality.
- · Counter transactions observation.
- · Business team understanding & observation.
- Banking halls meet & greet customers & general enquiries observation.
- Discussion with a Wealth Manager to understand the customer criteria.
- Observation of how Barclays communicate to staff & customers & contingency plan for the Coronavirus & the impact on our business operations.

#### EDUCATION

2021 Information Technology

Norwich College

IT Level 3 Foundation Diploma Extended

**Graded Distinction** 

2020 Information Technology

Norwich College

IT Level 3 Foundation Diploma

**Graded Distinction** 

2019 GCSE

Highgate Wood Secondary School

Computer Science - 5
Combined Science - 5
Media Studies - 5
Mathematics - 4

English Literature - 4

#### SKILLS

Website Development Intermediate Intermediate UI/UX Design Software Development Intermediate JavaScript Beginner **Computer Networking** Intermediate Python Intermediate .Net Intermediate **Project Management** Beginner CSS Intermediate Microsoft Azure Beginner Intermediate **Active Directory** Intermediate Problem-solving

Microsoft Office Advanced Communication Skills

Microsoft Server Intermediate Organization
Bootstrap 4 Beginner Teamwork
HTML5 Intermediate Leadership

# LANGUAGES

English Fluent Spanish Native